giftobit.com 2017-01-08

# GIFTOBIT | Home

GiftoBit Foundation Privacy Policy

##### Overview of our Privacy Policy

For those who want the short and relevant answer, we will always, ALWAYS, respect your privacy, your email address, and the information you give us. We’re not going to sell it, trade it, or abuse any information you submit to us. But I’m sure you’ve got some questions. Here’s our answers to what may be running through your mind.

##### How’s my information going to be used?

When you sign up on our Products or Services at giftobit.com, you’ll be receiving relevant information about GiftoBit Foundation (GiftoBit), invites to our weekly online training, news relating to your GiftoBit account (such as advice of new payments received, or new referrals who have used your referral link), and information about programs or products that pertain to Bitcoin, cryptocurrency, philanthropy and how you can create wealth online.

##### How do I to stop receiving emails from you in the future?

If you wish to stop receiving emails from us, you may unsubscribe at any time using the link provided at the bottom of all our emails. But if you’re still receiving emails from us, don’t worry, simply email us at [admin@giftobit.com.](mailto:admin@giftobit.com)

##### Who’s going to get my information?

Your information’s safe with us. So don’t worry about getting spam emails about Viagra or debt consolidation. We’ll never give out your email address or any of the information you submit on this site to anyone else. Only GiftoBit and your direct sponsor (whose referral link you used to register) will know your email address. GiftoBit is passionate about supporting peer-to-peer communications within our community, and your direct sponsor is responsible for answering any personal questions you may have, and assisting you in any way possible. Look forward to receiving your sponsor’s welcoming email!

##### What if I email you guys?

Your emails are confidential; we won’t share your email, data, or email address. It’s just between you and us.

##### How tech savvy are you guys when it comes to data security?

We’re real good. We have lots of administrative, managerial, and technical security measures put in place to protect your personal information. We’ve never had a breach of security and always strive for excellence in maintaining your privacy. We have also been authenticated by SiteLock, which gives extra security to our website. And you will notice, as one of our members, which we always encourage the use of Two Factor Authentication (2FA) to keep your account secure – and that is why you are emailed for confirmation every time you sign in to your GiftoBit back office.

##### Your privacy is very important to us

We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the Internet’s vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.  
We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our organization collects information from all end users of our Internet services (the “Services”), including those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts (“Visitors”) and those who may purchase Products and/or subscribe to the Service (“Members”). This Policy also explains what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of such information. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

##### We Appreciate Your Right to Anonymity 

Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Products or Services including name, address and telephone number. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process (or at any other time) is used primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Products and Services. Your information will never be licensed or sold to any third party. We appreciate your right to anonymity, and do not check if you are using your real or legal name when you register with us. GiftoBit operates as a Non-Government Organization (NGO) and we never provide disclosure of your personal information to any bodies, groups or persons.

##### Responses to email inquiries

When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to our organization, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Our organization does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

##### Public forums

Some parts of our site or related systems may enable you to participate in public services such as Facebook groups, blogs, and live events. Please use discretion when posting personal information about yourself when using these services. Be aware that when you disclose personal information at these sites, such as your name, member name, email address, etc., the information may be collected and used by others to send unsolicited email. The services are open to the public, and what you post there can be seen by anyone and is not protected. We try to moderate the comments as best we can but we can’t guarantee total control of the comments that you may receive while you participate in these services. Sometimes, you may find other people’s comments to be offensive, harmful or inaccurate.

##### Our organization’s commitment to data security

We implement a variety of administrative, managerial, and technical security measures to help protect your personal information. Our organization has various internal control standards which relate specifically to the handling of personal information. These include certain controls to help safeguard the information we collect online. Our employees are trained to understand and comply with these controls and we communicate our Privacy Notice, practices and guidelines to our employees. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you must also take steps to protect your information. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal information while you are on the Internet, and to make use of Two Factor Authentication (2FA) and to utilize an email service provider that provides you with 2FA. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining this information.

##### Revisions to this policy

Our organization reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting.

##### Where to direct questions about our privacy policy

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us by using the Support Ticket option in your GiftoBit back office.
